pinkpeonies.com 2019-07-06

# Privacy Policy - Rach Parcell

**Who we are**

Our website address is: http://68.183.31.82.

**What personal data we collect and why we collect it**

Comments: When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Media: If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

Contact forms

Cookies: If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

Embedded content from other websites: Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Analytics**

Who we share your data with:

How long we retain your data: If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

What rights you have over your data: If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Where we send your data: Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

––––

We do not share personal information with third-parties nor do I store information collected about your visit to Rachel Parcell for use other than to analyze content performance through the use of cookies, which you can turn off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings.

We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites that I may link to.

Rachel Parcell is affiliated with rewardStyle. A small commission is received on any sales of products that are linked on this site and across my social media. My work with brands and affiliates does not determine or influence my content as I only post content that I truly like and recommend.

**Please note that Rachel Parcell often receives samples and/or compensation for sponsored blog posts. If and when this occurs, it will be noted in the blog post.** For information on how to become a sponsor or to work with Rachel Parcell, please email us!
